esellerpro.com 2013-12-23

# Privacy Policy | eSellerPro

####  1\. INCORPORATION OF PRIVACY POLICY

1.1  Sandbourne Systems Limited, Pillar House, 113-115 Bath Road, Cheltenham, Gloucestershire, GL53 7LS, UK with Company No. 03227302 (‘Sandbourne’) is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and Sandbourne is compliant with the Data Protection Act 1998. This privacy policy (‘Privacy Policy’) explains how Sandbourne uses the information  Sandbourne collects about you and the procedures that Sandbourne has in place to safeguard your privacy. 

1.2 By using Sandbourne’s website www.esellerpro.com (‘Website’) whether you are purchasing and/or using any services provided by Sandbourne (‘Services’) through the Website, you consent to Sandbourne collecting and using identifying information about you. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions set out in this Privacy Policy, do not continue to use the Websites.

####  2 . THE INFORMATION SANDBOURNE COLLECTS AND HOW SANDBOURNE USES IT

2.1 When you visit the Website or obtain any Services offered on the Website, Sandbourne may collect information you provide including your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, type of Services obtained or webpages viewed and such other relevant information which Sandbourne deems necessary to process your order in respect of the Services. Where necessary, the information collected is transmitted in a secure manner to third parties to assist Sandbourne to provide you with the Services requested by you and to maintain the support services of Sandbourne. Information collected under this clause 2.1 is collected and is processed by us and Liberty Telemarketing to enable sales lead validation. 

2.2 Subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, Sandbourne protects all personal and financial data from being disclosed to any third parties except when required by law. In addition, Sandbourne may use your information to assist in the prevention of unlawful activities e.g. money laundering or activities which threaten Sandbourne’s Website or is adverse to your or Sandbourne’s interest.

2.3 Sandbourne may also use aggregate information and statistics, (but, which will not contain your identifying information) for the purposes of monitoring your usage of the Website in order to help Sandbourne develop the Website and the Services offered by Sandbourne. Sandbourne may provide such aggregate information to third parties.

2.4 Sandbourne may collect information which is based upon your behaviour and navigation on the Website. This information allows Sandbourne to carry out internal research on the users’ interest, demographics and behaviour so that Sandbourne can better understand, and in turn provide better information, products and services to you and other customers.

2.5 Sandbourne may also wish to provide you with information about special features featured on the Website or any other service or products Sandbourne thinks may be of interest to you. 

2.6 Sandbourne may also want to provide you with related information from third parties which it thinks may be of interest to you. 

2.7 If you do not wish Sandbourne to send you any information set out in Clauses 2.3 to 2.6 above, please send an e-mail to [jfrankish@seecoymarketing.com](mailto:jfrankish@seecoymarketing.com)

2.8 If you contact Sandbourne, Sandbourne may keep record of that correspondence.

2.9 Subject to the other provisions of this Privacy Policy and such other provisions specified on the Website, Sandbourne will not provide your information to other companies or organisations without your consent.

####  3 . USE OF COOKIES AND OTHER INFORMATION GATHERING TECHNOLOGIES

3.1  Sandbourne uses ‘cookies’ and other technologies to collect information on site to assist Sandbourne in monitoring Sandbourne’s web page flow, promotional effectiveness as well as to promote trust and safety.

3.2 Certain features on the Website are only available if you enable the cookie. Sandbourne also uses a cookie to assist it to provide information which is relevant to your interest.

3.3 You are free to decline Sandbourne’s cookies although that may impair certain features on the Website.

3.4 You can delete any cookies from your computer – refer to your internet browser’s help files.

3.5 Sandbourne may also track certain information through the use of JavaScript code and third party web site analytics providers.

3.6 Please note that the advertisers on Sandbourne website may also use cookies which Sandbourne have no control over.

####  4 . PROTECTING YOUR INFORMATION

4.1 The internet is not a secure medium.  However, Sandbourne has put in place various security procedures and strict policy rules to safeguard and protect your information from unauthorised and unlawful access and use. These security procedures and policy which are of the highest standards are continuously improved.

4.2 Notwithstanding the above, it should be appreciated that no system is entirely fool-proof and you should be careful when you reveal any confidential information to any third party.

####  5.  SALE OF COMPANY

5.1 If Sandbourne and/or this part of its business is sold or integrated with another business, your details may be disclosed to Sandbourne’s advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of Sandbourne.

####  6\. UPDATING YOUR DETAILS

6.1 If any of the information that you have provided to Sandbourne changes, for example if you change your e-mail address, name or payment details or if you wish to cancel your order, please let Sandbourne know the correct details by sending an e-mail to [jfrankish@seecoymarketing.com](mailto:jfrankish@seecoymarketing.com)

####  7\. OTHER TERMS

7.1 Owing to the global nature of the Internet infrastructure, the information you provide may be transferred in transit to countries outside the European Economic Area that do not have similar protections in place regarding your data and its use as set out in this Privacy Policy.  However, Sandbourne has taken the steps outlined above to try to improve the security of your information.  By using the Website, you consent to these transfers. 

7.2 Sandbourne supplies link to other websites. If you click on a link, you are not protected by this Privacy Policy and you are advised to read the privacy policy of the other website as they may differ from this Privacy Policy.

7.3 Sandbourne reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time as it deems necessary. In such event, Sandbourne will post such changes on the Website.

7.4 You have the right at any time to ask Sandbourne not to process your personal data for marketing purposes.

7.5 Sandbourne welcomes your views about the Website and its privacy policy.  If you would like to contact Sandbourne with any queries or comments please send an e-mail to [jfrankish@seecoymarketing.com](mailto:jfrankish@seecoymarketing.com)
